export const problemms = [
    {
    // "id": 0,
    question : 'Why We Use <br> Element ?',
    answers : [
    "To Make Text Bold",
    "To Make Text Italic",
    "To Add Breakline" , 
    "To Create Horizontal Line",
],
    right_answer: "To Add Breakline"
    },

{
    question : "Is <img> Element Has Attribute href ?",
    answers : [
        "Yes",
        "No Its For Anchor Tag <a>",
        "All Elements Has This Attribute",
        "Answer 1 And 3 Is Right",
],
    right_answer: "No Its For Anchor Tag <a>"},
    
{
    question : "How Can We Make Element Text Bold ?",
    answers : [
        "Putting It Inside <b> Tag",
        "Putting It Inside <strong> Tag",
        "Customizing It With Font-Weight Property In CSS",
        "All Answers Is Right",
],
    right_answer:  "All Answers Is Right"},


{
    question : "What Is The Right Hierarchy For Creating Part Of Page ?",
    answers : [
        "<h2> Then <p> Then <h1> Then <p> Then <h3> Then <p> Then <img>",
        "<h1> Then <p> Then <h3> Then <p> Then <h2> Then <p> Then <img>",
        "<h2> Then <p> Then <h3> Then <p> Then <h1> Then <p> Then <img>",
        "All Solutions Is Wrong",
],
    right_answer: "All Solutions Is Wrong"},

    {
    question : "How Can We Include External Page Inside Our HTML Page ?",
    answers : [
        "By Using Include in HTML",
        "By Using Load In HTML",
        "By Using iFrame Tag",
        "All Solutions Is Wrong",
],
    right_answer: "By Using iFrame Tag"},

    {
    question : "What Is The Tag That Not Exists in HTML ?",
    answers : [
        "<object>",
        "<basefont>",
        "<abbr>",
        "All Tags Is Exists in HTML",
],
    right_answer: "All Tags Is Exists in HTML"},

    {
    question : "How We Specify Document Type Of HTML5 Page ?",
    answers : [
        "<DOCTYPE html>",
        "<DOCTYPE html5>",
        "<!DOCTYPE html5>",
        "<!DOCTYPE html>",
],
    right_answer: "<!DOCTYPE html>"},

    {
    question :  "What Is The Element Thats Not Exists in HTML5 Semantics ?",
    answers : [
        "<article>",
        "<section>",
        "<blockquote>",
        "<aside>",
],
    right_answer:"<blockquote>"},

    {
    question :  "In HTML Can We Use This Way To Add Attributes ?",
    answers : [
        "<div class='class-name'>",
        "<div class=class-name>",
        "<div class=\"class-name\">",
        "All Is Right",
],
    right_answer:"All Is Right"},

    {
    question :  "How We Specify Document Type Of HTML5 Page ?",
    answers : [
        "<DOCTYPE html>",
        "<DOCTYPE html5>",
        "<!DOCTYPE html5>",
        "<!DOCTYPE html>",
],
    right_answer:"<!DOCTYPE html>"}
]




